Guide to the Big Band Arrangements Collection, 1990-2017 SC.2017.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Ten-Twelve Man Arrangements, V.
  - I Don't Want to Walk (Box 49, Folder 273)
  - I Get a Kick Out of You (Box 48, Folder 159)
  - I Write the Songs, Vocal (F) (Box 49, Folder 281)
  - I'll Be Seeing You (Box 48, Folder 192)
  - I'll String Along With You (Box 49, Folder 268)
  - If I Sing You a Love Song (Box 48, Folder 166)
  - In the Mood (Box 49, Folder 194)
  - Irish Medley (Box 48, Folder 173)
  - It Isn't Fair (Box 48, Folder 172)
  - Italian Medley (Box 49, Folder 300)
  - Jenny Lind Polka (Box 49, Folder 263)
  - Jersey Bounce (Box 49, Folder 222)
  - Josephine (Box 49, Folder 280)
  - Jumpin' at the Woodside (Box 49, Folder 229)
  - Kansas City (Box 48, Folder 135)
  - Knock Three Times (Box 49, Folder 251)
  - La Rosita (Box 49, Folder 214)
  - Lady (Box 48, Folder 101)
  - Little Brown Jug (Box 49, Folder 208)
  - Lollipops and Roses (Box 48, Folder 169)
  - Lonely Bull (Box 49, Folder 216)
  - Love is Here to Stay (Box 49, Folder 286)
  - Love to Keep You Warm (Box 49, Folder 247)
  - Mack the Knife (Box 49, Folder 207)
  - Magic in Moonlight (Box 48, Folder 153)
  - Marie (Box 49, Folder 285)
  - Medley-100 (Box 48, Folder 100)
  - Medley-100 (a) Darn That Dream (Box 48, Folder 100)
  - Medley-100 (b) Fools Rush In (Box 48, Folder 100)
  - Medley-100 (c) Love Me or Leave Me (Box 48, Folder 100)
  - Medley-105 (Box 48, Folder 105)
  - Medley-105 (a) Blue Hawaii (Box 48, Folder 105)
  - Medley-105 (b) Lovely Hula Hands (Box 48, Folder 105)
  - Medley-108 (Box 48, Folder 108)
  - Medley-108 (a) What I Did for Love (Box 48, Folder 108)
  - Medley-108 (b) Come In (Box 48, Folder 108)
  - Medley-112 (Box 48, Folder 112)
  - Medley-112 (a) Cecelia (Box 48, Folder 112)
  - Medley-112 (b) Johnson Rag (Box 48, Folder 112)
  - Medley-112 (c) My Melancholy Baby (Box 48, Folder 112)
  - Medley-113 (Box 48, Folder 113)
  - Medley-113 (a) Scotch and Soda (Box 48, Folder 113)
  - Medley-113 (b) All My Tomorrows (Box 48, Folder 113)
  - Medley-118 (Box 48, Folder 118)
  - Medley-118 (a) Cottage for Sale (Box 48, Folder 118)
  - Medley-118 (b) What Can I Say (Box 48, Folder 118)
  - Medley-121 (Sammy Kay) (Box 48, Folder 121)
  - Medley-121 (a) Hawaiian Sunset (Box 48, Folder 121)
  - Medley-121 (b) Far Away Look in Your Eyes (Box 48, Folder 121)
  - Medley-121 (c) Honestly (Box 48, Folder 121)
  - Medley-123 (Box 48, Folder 123)
  - Medley-123 (a) Fascination (Box 48, Folder 123)
  - Medley-123 (b) Charmaine (Box 48, Folder 123)
  - Medley-123 (c) If You Were the Only Girl in the World (Box 48, Folder 123)
  - Medley-125 (Box 48, Folder 125)
  - Medley-125 (a) Stairway to the Stars (Box 48, Folder 125)
  - Medley-125 (b) Manhattan (Box 48, Folder 125)
  - Medley-127 (Box 48, Folder 127)
  - Medley-127 (a) Hands Across the Table (Box 48, Folder 127)
  - Medley-127 (b) Baby's Prayer (Box 48, Folder 127)
  - Medley-127 (c) Home (Box 48, Folder 127)
  - Medley-132 (Box 48, Folder 132)
  - Medley-132 (a) Godfather (Box 48, Folder 132)
  - Medley-132 (b) Summer of '42 (Box 48, Folder 132)
  - Medley-133 (Box 48, Folder 133)
  - Medley-133 (a) Night and Day (Box 48, Folder 133)
  - Medley-133 (b) Velvet Moon (Box 48, Folder 133)
  - Medley-134 (Box 48, Folder 134)
  - Medley-134 (a) Sentimental Journey (Box 48, Folder 134)
  - Medley-134 (b) Sophisticated Swing (Box 48, Folder 134)
  - Medley-137 (Box 48, Folder 137)
  - Medley-137 (a) Dancing on the Ceiling (Box 48, Folder 137)
  - Medley-137 (b) You and Night and Music (Box 48, Folder 137)
  - Medley-137 (c) September in the Rain (Box 48, Folder 137)
  - Medley-140 (Box 48, Folder 140)
  - Medley-140 (a) A Fine Romance (Box 48, Folder 140)
  - Medley-140 (b) How Many Hearts (Box 48, Folder 140)
  - Medley-140 (c) I Cried for You (Box 48, Folder 140)
  - Medley-141 (a) Green Grass (Box 48, Folder 141)
  - Medley-141 (b) Good Times (Box 48, Folder 141)
  - Medley-142 (Box 48, Folder 142)
  - Medley-142 (a) Careless (Box 48, Folder 142)
  - Medley-142 (b) Lilacs in the Rain (Box 48, Folder 142)
  - Medley-143 (Box 48, Folder 143)
  - Medley-143 (a) Harvest Moon (Box 48, Folder 143)
  - Medley-143 (b) Sleepy Time Gal (Box 48, Folder 143)
  - Medley-143 (c) Swingin' Down the Lane (Box 48, Folder 143)
  - Medley-145 (Box 48, Folder 145)
  - Medley-145 (a) Miss You (Box 48, Folder 145)
  - Medley-145 (b) As Time Goes By (Box 48, Folder 145)
  - Medley-148 (Box 48, Folder 148)
  - Medley-148 (a) The Gypsy (Box 48, Folder 148)
  - Medley-148 (b) 'Till Then (Box 48, Folder 148)
  - Medley-152 (Box 48, Folder 152)
  - Medley-152 (a) Party's Over (Box 48, Folder 152)
  - Medley-152 (b) Goodnight Sweetheart (Box 48, Folder 152)
  - Medley-155 (Box 48, Folder 155)
  - Medley-155 (a) Moonlight Serenade (Box 48, Folder 155)
  - Medley-155 (b) Serenade in Blue (Box 48, Folder 155)
  - Medley-162 (Box 48, Folder 162)
  - Medley-162 (a) They Say It's Wonderful (Box 48, Folder 162)
  - Medley-162 (b) Mam'selle (Box 48, Folder 162)
  - Medley-168 (Box 48, Folder 168)
  - Medley-168 (a) Old Cape Cod (Box 48, Folder 168)
  - Medley-168 (b) Wishing (Box 48, Folder 168)
  - Medley-170 (Box 48, Folder 170)
  - Medley-170 (a) Jeanine (Box 48, Folder 170)
  - Medley-170 (b) Put Your Dreams Away (Box 48, Folder 170)
  - Medley-180 (Box 48, Folder 180)
  - Medley-180 (a) Be Happy (Box 48, Folder 180)
  - Medley-180 (b) Tea for Two (Box 48, Folder 180)
  - Medley-185 (Box 48, Folder 185)
  - Medley-185 (a) Siboney (Box 48, Folder 185)
  - Medley-185 (b) Besame Mucho (Box 48, Folder 185)
  - Medley-193 (Box 48, Folder 193)
  - Medley-193 (a) Christmas Song (Box 48, Folder 193)
  - Medley-193 (b) White Christmas (Box 48, Folder 193)
  - Medley-195 (Box 49, Folder 195)
  - Medley-195 (a) Sammy Kaye (Box 49, Folder 195)
  - Medley-195 (b) Tommy Dorsey (Box 49, Folder 195)
  - Medley-195 (c) Harry James (Box 49, Folder 195)
  - Medley-205 (Box 49, Folder 205)
  - Medley-205 (a) For You (Box 49, Folder 205)
  - Medley-205 (b) Oh How I Miss You (Box 49, Folder 205)
  - Medley-205 (c) Shanty Town (Box 49, Folder 205)
  - Medley-212 (Box 49, Folder 212)
  - Medley-212 (a) Tango of the Roses (Box 49, Folder 212)
  - Medley-212 (b) Orchids in the Moonlight (Box 49, Folder 212)
  - Medley-235 (Box 49, Folder 235)
  - Medley-235 (b) Green Dolphin Street (Box 49, Folder 235)
  - Medley-235 (a) At Last (Box 49, Folder 235)
  - Medley-241 (Box 49, Folder 241)
  - Medley-241 (a) Whispering (Box 49, Folder 241)
  - Medley-241 (b) Blue (Box 49, Folder 241)
  - Medley-241 (c) Margie (Box 49, Folder 241)
  - Medley-258 (Box 49, Folder 258)
  - Medley-258 (a) Brasilia (Box 49, Folder 258)
  - Medley-258 (b) So What's New (Box 49, Folder 258)
  - Medley-270 (Box 49, Folder 270)
  - Medley-270 (a) Hucklebuck (Box 49, Folder 270)
  - Medley-270 (b) Ara Dara Honeymoon (Box 49, Folder 270)
  - Medley-270 (c) Mama Loves Papa (Box 49, Folder 270)
  - Medley-283 (Box 49, Folder 283)
  - Medley-283 (a) Oh What It Seemed to Be (Box 49, Folder 283)
  - Medley-283 (b) My Devotion (Box 49, Folder 283)
  - Medley-283 (c) East of the Sun (Box 49, Folder 283)
  - Misirlou (Box 49, Folder 233)
  - Misty (Larry Faith) (Box 49, Folder 278)
  - Misty Blue (Box 48, Folder 165)
  - My Kind of Girl (Box 49, Folder 282)
  - My Prayer (Box 48, Folder 111)
  - Nearness of You (Box 48, Folder 130)
  - New York, New York (Box 49, Folder 250)
  - Never on Sunday (Box 49, Folder 221)
  - Next One Hundred Years (Box 49, Folder 265)
  - Old Fashioned Way (Box 48, Folder 106)
  - Old Fashioned Way (Box 48, Folder 186)
  - Out of Nowhere (Box 48, Folder 188)
  - Patricia (Box 48, Folder 177)
  - Perfume Medley (Box 48, Folder 124)
  - Polka Dots and Moonbeams (Larry Faith) (Box 49, Folder 277)
  - Poor Butterfly (Box 48, Folder 122)
  - Rainy Day (Harry Boles) (Box 49, Folder 237)
  - Ray's Blues (Box 48, Folder 103)
  - Red Roses for a Blue Lady (Box 48, Folder 139)
  - Rise (Box 48, Folder 110)
  - Satin Doll (Box 49, Folder 204)
  - Satin Doll (Box 49, Folder 284)
  - Say You'll Wait Until Tomorrow (Box 48, Folder 126)
  - Sexy Eyes (Box 49, Folder 274)
  - Shiny Stockings (Box 49, Folder 223)
  - South (Box 48, Folder 129)
  - Southern Fried (Box 49, Folder 253)
  - Something Stupid (Box 48, Folder 119)
  - Somewhere My Love (Box 48, Folder 171)
  - Spanish Eyes (Box 49, Folder 242)
  - Spanish Eyes (Box 49, Folder 252)
  - Stairway to the Stars (Box 48, Folder 151)
  - Stompin' at the Savoy (Box 49, Folder 196)
  - String of Pearls (Box 49, Folder 203)
  - Summer Wind (Box 49, Folder 245)
  - Sway (Box 49, Folder 210)
  - Sweet Caroline (Box 49, Folder 206)
  - Swinging Down the Lane (Box 48, Folder 184)
  - Talk of the Town (Box 48, Folder 156)
  - Tangerine (Box 49, Folder 272)
  - Tango of the Roses (Box 48, Folder 109)
  - Tea for Two (Box 48, Folder 117)
  - The Most Beautiful Girl (Box 49, Folder 248)
  - This Love of Mine (Box 48, Folder 128)
  - Tiajuana Taxi (Box 49, Folder 219)
  - Tie a Yellow Ribbon 'Round the Ol' Oak Tree (Box 49, Folder 220)
  - To Each His Own (Box 48, Folder 189)
  - Too Much, Too Little, Too Late (Box 48, Folder 144)
  - Trumpet Cha Cha (Box 48, Folder 182)
  - Tuxedo Junction (Box 49, Folder 232)
  - Village Tavern Polka (Box 49, Folder 271)
  - Waltz Medley (Box 49, Folder 227)
  - Waltz Medley (Box 49, Folder 236)
  - Watch What Happens (Box 48, Folder 136)
  - Westwind Polka (Box 49, Folder 264)
  - Where is the Love (Box 48, Folder 175)
  - Winchester Cathedral (Box 49, Folder 266)
  - Woodchopper's Ball (Box 49, Folder 198)
  - Yellow Bird (Box 48, Folder 163)
  - Yellow Bird (Box 49, Folder 230)
  - Yesterday Once More (Box 49, Folder 215)
  - You'll Never Find (Box 48, Folder 158)
  - You're Driving Me Crazy (Box 49, Folder 226)
  - You're Nobody (Box 48, Folder 138)
- Two Way Arrangements, VI.
  - Famous Themes (Box 50, Folder 249)
  - Gong Rock (Box 50, Folder 70)
  - Helena Polka (Box 50, Folder 43)
  - Irish Waltz Medley (Box 50, Folder 246)
  - Medley-200 (Box 50, Folder 200)
  - Medley-200 (a) Button Up Your Overcoat (Box 50, Folder 200)
  - Medley-200 (b) Tip Toe Through the Tulips (Box 50, Folder 200)
  - Medley-200 (c) Toot, Toot, Tootsie Goodbye (Box 50, Folder 200)
  - Medley-204 (Box 50, Folder 204)
  - Medley-204 (a) Made for Each Other (Box 50, Folder 204)
  - Medley-204 (b) You Belong to My Heart (Box 50, Folder 204)
  - Medley-204 (c) Magic is the Moonlight (Box 50, Folder 204)
  - Medley-229 (Box 50, Folder 229)
  - Medley-229 (a) Tennessee Waltz (Box 50, Folder 229)
  - Medley-229 (b) Vaya Con Dios (Box 50, Folder 229)
  - Medley-229 (c) Mexicali Rose (Box 50, Folder 229)
  - Medley-205 (Box 50, Folder 205)
  - Medley-205 (a) Do You Ever Think of Me (Box 50, Folder 205)
  - Medley-205 (b) Avalon (Box 50, Folder 205)
  - Medley-205 (c) Linger awhile (Box 50, Folder 205)
  - Medley-226 (Box 50, Folder 226)
  - Medley-226 (a) Baby Face (Box 50, Folder 226)
  - Medley-226 (b) Bye Bye Blues (Box 50, Folder 226)
  - Medley-226 (c) Five Foot Two (Box 50, Folder 226)
  - Medley-227 (Box 50, Folder 227)
  - Medley-227 (a) True Love (Box 50, Folder 227)
  - Medley-227 (b) Melody of Love (Box 50, Folder 227)
  - Medley-227 (c) My Dear (Box 50, Folder 227)
  - Medley-235 (Box 50, Folder 235)
  - Medley-235 (a) Pretend (Box 50, Folder 235)
  - Medley-235 (b) Arrivederci Roma (Box 50, Folder 235)
  - Medley-235 (c) Besame Mucho (Box 50, Folder 235)
  - Medley-238 (Box 50, Folder 238)
  - Medley-238 (a) Around the World (Box 50, Folder 238)
  - Medley-238 (b) Fascination (Box 50, Folder 238)
  - Medley-239 (Box 50, Folder 239)
  - Medley-239 (a) Carolina Moon (Box 50, Folder 239)
  - Medley-239 (b) The Waltz You Saved for Me (Box 50, Folder 239)
  - Medley-239 (c) Paradise (Box 50, Folder 239)
  - Medley-240 (Box 50, Folder 240)
  - Medley-240 (a) Dancero (Box 50, Folder 240)
  - Medley-240 (b) Adios (Box 50, Folder 240)
  - Medley-241 (Box 50, Folder 241)
  - Medley-241 (a) Christmas Song (Box 50, Folder 241)
  - Medley-241 (b) White Christmas (Box 50, Folder 241)
  - Medley-242 (Box 50, Folder 242)
  - Medley-242 (a) Have You Ever Been Lonely (Box 50, Folder 242)
  - Medley-242 (b) I Cried for You (Box 50, Folder 242)
  - Medley-242 (c) Sit Right Down (Box 50, Folder 242)
  - Medley-243 (Box 50, Folder 243)
  - Medley-243 (a) Me and My Shadow (Box 50, Folder 243)
  - Medley-243 (b) Little Girl (Box 50, Folder 243)
  - Medley-243 (c) Should I (Box 50, Folder 243)
  - Medley-244 (Box 50, Folder 244)
  - Medley-244 (a) Small Hotel (Box 50, Folder 244)
  - Medley-244 (b) Dancing on the Ceiling (Box 50, Folder 244)
  - Medley-245 (Box 50, Folder 245)
  - Medley-245 (a) Toyland (Box 50, Folder 245)
  - Medley-245 (b) Where the Blue of the Night (Box 50, Folder 245)
  - Medley-245 (c) When I Grow Too Old to Dream (Box 50, Folder 245)
  - Medley-247 (Box 50, Folder 247)
  - Medley-247 (a) Moonglow (Box 50, Folder 247)
  - Medley-247 (b) Picnic (Box 50, Folder 247)
  - Medley-248 (Box 50, Folder 248)
  - Medley-248 (a) When Day is Done (Box 50, Folder 248)
  - Medley-248 (b) Where or When (Box 50, Folder 248)
  - Medley-248 (c) Love Walked In (Box 50, Folder 248)
  - More (Box 50, Folder 250)
  - Nearness of You (Box 50, Folder 151)
  - Satin Doll (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Star Eyes (Box 50, Folder 60)
- Three Way Arrangements, VII.
  - 1492 (Box 51, Folder 313)
  - A Media Luz (Box 51, Folder 120)
  - Address Unknown (Box 51, Folder 86)
  - Adios Muchachos (Box 51, Folder 118)
  - After the Lovin' (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Always In My Heart (Box 51, Folder 101)
  - And Then It's Heaven (Box 51, Folder 307)
  - Angel Eyes (Box 51, Folder 352)
  - Anytime (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - Autumn Nocturne (Box 51, Folder 49)
  - Baby Please Come Home (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Begin the Beguine (Box 51, Folder 127)
  - Blue Skies (Box 51, Folder 320)
  - Blues (Box 51, Folder 302)
  - Bourbon Street Parade (Box 51, Folder 139)
  - Boy Meets Horn (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Brown Eyes Blue (Box 51, Folder 117)
  - Canadian Sunset (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Can't Take My Eyes Off of You (Box 51, Folder 351)
  - Celestial Blues (Woody Herman) (Box 51, Folder 136)
  - Cha Cha Flamenco (Box 51, Folder 121)
  - Cocktails for Two (Box 51, Folder 111)
  - Come Rain or Come Shine (Box 51, Folder 76)
  - Coquette (Box 51, Folder 54)
  - Crazy Love (Lenny Mehal) (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - Cry Me a River (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - Cunningham Cha Cha (Box 51, Folder 124)
  - Deep Purple (Box 51, Folder 78)
  - El Choclo (Box 51, Folder 115)
  - For Me, For You, Forevermore (Box 51, Folder 51)
  - Forgiveness (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Gone With the Wind (Box 51, Folder 79)
  - Harlem Nocturne (Box 51, Folder 43)
  - Harlem Nocturne (Box 51, Folder 130)
  - Heartaches (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - Hey Jealous Lover (Box 51, Folder 316)
  - I Can't Get Started (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - I Surrender Dear (Box 51, Folder 46)
  - I Want to Be Happy (Box 51, Folder 102)
  - I'm Through With Love (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - Imagination (Box 51, Folder 52)
  - Jazz Me Blues (Box 51, Folder 213)
  - Johnson Rag (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - La Cumparsita (Box 51, Folder 103)
  - La Paloma (Box 51, Folder 104)
  - Laura (Box 51, Folder 41)
  - Let's Do It (Box 51, Folder 131)
  - Lover Man (Box 51, Folder 61)
  - Makin' Whoopie (Box 51, Folder 135)
  - Mama Inez (Box 51, Folder 109)
  - Margie (Box 51, Folder 89)
  - Me and My Shadow, Vocal Band (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Medley-1 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Medley-1 (a) Drifting and Dreaming (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Medley-1 (b) I'll See You in My Dreams (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Medley-1 (c) Goodnight Sweetheart (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Medley-2 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Medley-2 (a) Remember Me (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Medley-2 (b) We Just Couldn't Say Goodbye (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Medley-4 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Medley-4 (a) Oh What it Seemed to Be (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Medley-4 (b) Gee Its Good to Hold You (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Medley-5 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Medley-5 (a) You Are Too Beautiful (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Medley-5 (b) East of the Sun (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Medley-5 (c) So What's New (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Medley-6 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Medley-6 (a) June in January (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Medley-6 (b) Nevertheless (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Medley-7 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Medley-7 (a) Little White Lies (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Medley-7 (b) These Foolish Things (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Medley-7 (c) September in the Rain (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Medley-10 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Medley-10 (a) This Love of Mine (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Medley-10 (b) There Are Such Things (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Medley-12 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Medley-12 (a) Am I Blue (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Medley-12 (a) All of Me (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Medley-14 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Medley-14 (a) I've Grown Accustomed to Her Face (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Medley-14 (b) On the Street Where You Live (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Medley-15 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Medley-15 (a) Cynthia (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Medley-15 (b) We'll Gather Lilacs (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Medley-16 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Medley-16 (a) I'm Getting Sentimental Over You (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Medley-16 (b) With the Wind (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Medley-16 (c) Trust in Me (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Medley-19 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Medley-19 (a) Do You Ever Think of Me (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Medley-19 (b) Maybe (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Medley-20 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Medley-20 (a) My Prayer (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Medley-20 (b) My Happiness (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Medley-20 (c) The Night is Young (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Medley-26 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Medley-26 (a) From This Day Forward (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Medley-26 (b) We'll Gather Lilacs (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Medley-28 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Medley-28 (a) This is Always (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Medley-28 (b) Guilty (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Medley-35 (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - Medley-35 (a) Among My Souvenirs (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - Medley-35 (b) Memories of You (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - Medley-35 (c) Just One More Chance (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - Medley-39 (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - Medley-39 (a) My Silent Love (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - Medley-39 (b) Body and Soul (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - Medley-39 (c) Stardust (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - Medley-40 (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - Medley-40 (a) I Still Get a Thrill (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - Medley-40 (b) Jealous (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - Medley-40 (c) Poor Butterfly (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - Medley-42 (Box 51, Folder 42)
  - Medley-42 (a) Moonglow (Box 51, Folder 42)
  - Medley-42 (b) I Only Have Eyes For You (Box 51, Folder 42)
  - Medley-42 (c) Stars Fell on Alabama (Box 51, Folder 42)
  - Medley-45 (Box 51, Folder 45)
  - Medley-45 (a) Dancing in the Dark (Box 51, Folder 45)
  - Medley-45 (b) You Were Meant for Me (Box 51, Folder 45)
  - Medley-45 (c) A Pretty Girl (Box 51, Folder 45)
  - Medley-47 (Box 51, Folder 47)
  - Medley-47 (a) Ghost of a Chance (Box 51, Folder 47)
  - Medley-47 (b) That Old Feeling (Box 51, Folder 47)
  - Medley-47 (c) Once in a While (Box 51, Folder 47)
  - Medley-48 (Box 51, Folder 48)
  - Medley-48 (a) Night (Box 51, Folder 48)
  - Medley-48 (b) Sweet and Lovely (Box 51, Folder 48)
  - Medley-50 (Box 51, Folder 50)
  - Medley-50 (a) Harbor Lights (Box 51, Folder 50)
  - Medley-50 (b) Don't Blame Me (Box 51, Folder 50)
  - Medley-50 (c) That's My Desire (Box 51, Folder 50)
  - Medley-53 (Lenny Mehal) (Box 51, Folder 53)
  - Medley-53 (a) 'Till There Was You (Box 51, Folder 53)
  - Medley-53 (b) I Know (Box 51, Folder 53)
  - Medley-53 (c) The Last Dance (Box 51, Folder 53)
  - Medley-55 (Box 51, Folder 55)
  - Medley-55 (a) Dancing on the Ceiling (Box 51, Folder 55)
  - Medley-55 (b) 'Swonderful (Box 51, Folder 55)
  - Medley-55 (c) Manhattan (Box 51, Folder 55)
  - Medley-57 (Box 51, Folder 57)
  - Medley-57 (a) Only You (Box 51, Folder 57)
  - Medley-57 (b) Someone (Box 51, Folder 57)
  - Medley-57 (c) Summer Dreams (Box 51, Folder 57)
  - Medley-62 (Box 51, Folder 62)
  - Medley-62 (a) Penthouse Serenade (Box 51, Folder 62)
  - Medley-62 (b) Blanket of Blue (Box 51, Folder 62)
  - Medley-62 (c) Stairway to the Stars (Box 51, Folder 62)
  - Medley-63 (Box 51, Folder 63)
  - Medley-63 (a) All Through the Day (Box 51, Folder 63)
  - Medley-63 (b) If I Had a Wishing Ring (Box 51, Folder 63)
  - Medley-65 (Box 51, Folder 65)
  - Medley-65 (a) Lovely to Look At (Box 51, Folder 65)
  - Medley-65 (b) Why I Was Born (Box 51, Folder 65)
  - Medley-65 (c) Why Do I Love You (Box 51, Folder 65)
  - Medley-66 (Box 51, Folder 66)
  - Medley-66 (a) Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer (Box 51, Folder 66)
  - Medley-66 (b) Winter Wonderland (Box 51, Folder 66)
  - Medley-66 (c) White Christmas (Box 51, Folder 66)
  - Medley-67 (Box 51, Folder 67)
  - Medley-67 (a) Charmaine (Box 51, Folder 67)
  - Medley-67 (b) Diane (Box 51, Folder 67)
  - Medley-67 (c) Ramona (Box 51, Folder 67)
  - Medley-68 (Box 51, Folder 68)
  - Medley-68 (a) Release Me (Box 51, Folder 68)
  - Medley-68 (b) Somewhere My Love (Box 51, Folder 68)
  - Medley-68 (c) Now I Know (Box 51, Folder 68)
  - Medley-70 (Box 51, Folder 70)
  - Medley-70 (a) Dolores (Box 51, Folder 70)
  - Medley-70 (b) Carolina in the Morning (Box 51, Folder 70)
  - Medley-70 (c) Object of My Affection (Box 51, Folder 70)
  - Medley-72 (Box 51, Folder 72)
  - Medley-72 (a) Dancing in the Dark (Box 51, Folder 72)
  - Medley-72 (b) You Were Meant for Me (Box 51, Folder 72)
  - Medley-72 (c) Silent Love (Box 51, Folder 72)
  - Medley-80 (Box 51, Folder 80)
  - Medley-80 (a) Button Up Your Overcoat (Box 51, Folder 80)
  - Medley-80 (b) Cream in My Coffee (Box 51, Folder 80)
  - Medley-80 (c) The Best Things in Life Are Free (Box 51, Folder 80)
  - Medley-83 (Box 51, Folder 83)
  - Medley-83 (a) Mood Indigo (Box 51, Folder 83)
  - Medley-83 (b) I Let a Song Go Out of My Heart (Box 51, Folder 83)
  - Medley-83 (c) In a Sentimental Mood (Box 51, Folder 83)
  - Medley-84 (Box 51, Folder 84)
  - Medley-84 (a) June Night (Box 51, Folder 84)
  - Medley-84 (b) Please (Box 51, Folder 84)
  - Medley-84 (c) Where or When (Box 51, Folder 84)
  - Medley-87 (Box 51, Folder 87)
  - Medley-87 (a) In the Mood for Love (Box 51, Folder 87)
  - Medley-87 (b) Stairway to the Stars (Box 51, Folder 87)
  - Medley-91 (Box 51, Folder 91)
  - Medley-91 (a) Said it Again (Box 51, Folder 91)
  - Medley-91 (b) Moon Song (Box 51, Folder 91)
  - Medley-129 (Box 51, Folder 129)
  - Medley-129 (a) Stars Fell on Alabama (Box 51, Folder 129)
  - Medley-129 (b) If I Had You (Box 51, Folder 129)
  - Medley-200 (Box 51, Folder 200)
  - Medley-200 (a) Girl of My Dreams (Box 51, Folder 200)
  - Medley-200 (b) My Isle of Golden Dreams (Box 51, Folder 200)
  - Medley-201 (Box 51, Folder 201)
  - Medley-201 (a) Memories (Box 51, Folder 201)
  - Medley-201 (b) Carolina Moon (Box 51, Folder 201)
  - Medley-203 (Box 51, Folder 203)
  - Medley-203 (a) Always (Box 51, Folder 203)
  - Medley-203 (b) Together (Box 51, Folder 203)
  - Medley-300 (Box 51, Folder 300)
  - Medley-300 (a) Button Up Your Overcoat (Box 51, Folder 300)
  - Medley-300 (b) The Best Things in Life Are Free (Box 51, Folder 300)
  - Medley-311 (Box 51, Folder 311)
  - Medley-311 (a) Paper Moon (Box 51, Folder 311)
  - Medley-311 (b) Sundown (Box 51, Folder 311)
  - Medley-311 (c) When My Sugar (Box 51, Folder 311)
  - Medley-350 (Box 51, Folder 350)
  - Medley-350 (a) Old Hawaii (Box 51, Folder 350)
  - Medley-350 (b) Beyond the Reef (Box 51, Folder 350)
  - Medley-350 (c) Lovely Hula Hands (Box 51, Folder 350)
  - Medley-353 (Box 51, Folder 353)
  - Medley-353 (a) Mountain Greenery (Box 51, Folder 353)
  - Medley-353 (b) The Lady is a Tramp (Box 51, Folder 353)
  - Medley-353 (c) This Can't Be Love (Box 51, Folder 353)
  - Miami Beach (Box 51, Folder 112)
  - Moonlight Serenade (Box 51, Folder 85)
  - Mr. Success (Box 51, Folder 319)
  - Music (Box 51, Folder 73)